□ (+7) 925 203-27-42 | ■ nevarko.ad@phystech.edu | • AlexanderNevarko

Summary_

I am a 4-year student of MIPT. I am keen on programming, physics, maths and mostly all other technical sciences. I have an analytical mindset, have an entrepreneur spirit and a lot of will to create new interesting projects. I am looking forward to learning new areas of computer science, such as Data Science, High Load systems, Distributed systems, applied mathematics.

Experience_

Acronis Moscow, Russia

INTERN IN RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT

Sep 2019 - Present

• Developing REST API Intelligent Fuzzing tester as a graduate work. The tool may become an opensource competitor for an analog from Microsoft Research RESTLer.

Laboratory for modeling and designing special computing architectures

MIPT, Moscow, Russia

PYTHON DEVELOPER / PHYSICIST

Jul 2019 - Present

- Integrated a physical model of a ballistic rocket into the project.
- Developing a physical engine for phased antenna arrays.
- Improved a graphical phased antenna array geometry redactor.

MIPT, Moscow, Russia

HEAD OF IT-DEPARTMENT

May 2017 - Dec 2018

• Created an access system for public places, such as washing rooms in dormitories, consisting of a web-site and an electronic locker for key-cards (frtk.mipt.ru).

School Self-government Council

Lyceum 2, Moscow, Russia

HEAD OF SCHOOL SELF-GOVERNMENT COUNCIL

Sep 2015 - Jun 2016

- Implemented a humanitarian aid project for Russian-language schools in Kyrgyzstan. About 5 tons of Russian-language textbooks were collected in Moscow and distributed to 14 schools in Kyrgyzstan.
- · Founded a charity fair, the profit of which went to help children with health problems in orphanages.

Education

Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology

Dolgoprudny, Russia

DEPARTMENT OF RADIO ELECTRONICS AND CYBERNETICS

2016 - 2020

SUB-DEPARTMENT OF THEORETICAL AND APPLIED INFORMATICS, BASE ORGANIZATION - ACRONIS

2018 - 2020

Skills____

Programming Python, Go, C/C++, git, Linux

Maths/Physics Linear algebra, mathematical analysis, general physics, quantum mechanics, etc.

Soft Skills Leadership, communications, teamwork **Languges** English (upper intermediate), German (B1)

Honors & Awards

2018 **Winner of the Russian stage**, Red Bull Basement University

Moscow / Berlin Sochi, Russia

2016 **Final Stage Winner**, Russian National Physics School Olympiad